Dear children, today is 15th August.
Our country became independent on this day.  So the national anthem should be started on this occasion.
Jana Gana Mana Adhinayak
Jai Hey Bharat.
Hey brother, what happens by offering water?
Hey brother, the more water one offers in the month of Sawan, the
more beautiful wife Mahadev becomes pleased with him.
[Music] I
got a glimpse of you,
but what happened?
One
my [music] one
[laughter]
you're in your right mind.  How did you dare to
do this?
But Baba, what did I do?
Why did you unfollow me on Instagram
?
[laughter] I'll block you right now.
Baba, please look at my horoscope.
Son, there is a lot of money in your horoscope.
Brother, please remove ₹00 from my horoscope.
[laughter] That's me,
brother.  [Laughter]
Brother, the tricolor or money, wait a minute.
Look at this money.  This is Jain ji of our country and
this is the youth of our country.  How many people have fallen for
money.  Look at this.
[Music]
Mummy,
don't call me Mummy.  We are angry with you.
Ok.  Sir, I know your husband is asking for food.
Go and give it to me.  [laughter]
I love you.
But I am 2 years older than you.  It doesn't matter to me.
But my family will not agree.   If
the love was true, everyone would agree.   Do you
love me so much?   I
love you more than my life.   I
swear to Allah, brother, I am a boy.  If
I were a girl, I would elope and marry you.
[laughter]
Stop stop stop stop.
Wait, be patient.
Oh so sweet thank you, I am
watching your welcome, I am giving it in a box to the masters
and in our hands that too is just a laddu
and wait now
listen, you all know what is there tomorrow
?  Yes ma'am it is 15th August.
Okay, then come tomorrow all ready and as
15th August is celebrated once a year,
we have decided to
feed you all to your heart's content and also give you some to take home.
Okay ma'am.
But wait a second
[laughter]
he's new in the neighborhood, right?  Oh, is she your brother or sister
?  Not there.  And people like you shouldn't even have it.
Hey brother, tomorrow is Rakshabandhan, that's why I was
telling you, my house is next door, come, my
sister will wait
[laughs]
Uncle, if you permit me, then you can become my son-in-law,
depression,
hey, he won't become my son-in-law, I want to become him
[laughs]
ok
uncle, if you permit me, then I will become your daughter
's slave, friend, a
slave has to become a slave after marriage.   One has to
become a slave.  Right now I want to become a husband.
Husband [laughs]
Uncle, if you permit, I will become your daughter
's husband.
You have spoiled everything, I will do it.
[Music]
Son, you are going to office, so please bring your sister from her
in-laws' house in the evening.   I will take
this also.  I will drop her at her parents' house.
And if he takes her away, who will do the household work
?
If I bring my sister here,
who will do the work there?
His breath will do it.
So it will breathe here too, right?
Bye Bye Tata.  Goodbye.
Hey brother,
yes, I just
messaged the girl you used to flirt with in school.  [laughter]
Hey brother, what happened to 1 minute, 1 minute?
Look brother, the girl who is destined to get it is the one who gets it.
Hey brother, the
girl will come and go but only
mom will bring her own girl.  Congratulations
[laughter]
But what is this guy doing here?   The
climax is yet to come.
[laughter]
I'm brother
picked up the leaf.  [laughter]
Hello, yes, say that.   Is it
₹100?   Yes it is.
Brother, it's okay.
And wait for now.  The climax is yet to come.
[bell ringing]
Looks like it's been sent.
[laughter]
That's a story too.  Fish is the queen of water.
Life is its water.  Isn't it
uninvited to go to his wedding?   There is
no seed in peanuts, we are not your grandfather.  He
said, I cannot live
without you.  Today his two children came and that too without me.
Brother, give me a plate of tea.
What is this?  Now you see, now you take it,
hey, when should I put it,
hey, I told you one plate of tea, so take it, take one
plate of tea,
hey, give me one plate and one tea, both
separately
[laughs] take it, take it
[screaming sound] you bastard, hey,
bring a biscuit also,
yes I am bringing it,
hey [screaming sound] this is breaking.  Give me
another one.
[Music]
You're gone, son.   I laughed.
[laughs]
And if the government
allows girls to put their favorite photo on their Aadhaar card, then
girls' Aadhaar cards will look something like this.
How?  [screaming]
What happened to me?   I have
not met my wife and children for 20 years.
Because the marriage did not happen.
America [laughs]
Today we would say, what are you?
Baby, if you truly love me,
you will leave your marriage and
come to me.  If you truly love me, you will
leave this marriage and come to me.  If you
really love me then
you will leave your marriage and come to me.
Brother, you called all your three girlfriends.  What
if even one of the three doesn't come?
Brother called three.  One of the three will
come.
Bhai
le [music] here it is.
Leaving the whole world behind, I came to your bond.
Leaving all the bonds.
I have come to you.   The
whole world came and thought, your
brother, I wanted to join the gym, how much would the fee be, it is
₹500 brother,
brother, can two of us do it for ₹500, oh
no brother, you guys will not be able to adjust,
oh brother, there is no problem, we will do it, we will do it
[laughs]
I am here brother.  [laughter]
[laughter]
Wait a minute
my love, look at this, how is it? No, not
good. [screaming sound]
And how is this one?
How are you picking mangoes?  Will
you buy vegetables?  [laughter]
Okay, and tell me this one.
This is also useless, your ruin.
[laughter]
Hey,
you're gone now, son, you're gone now, look,
I'm here [laughter]
brother,
someone has died in the village.
And wait for now.
Now I will eat the whole vegetable with great force.
I will eat Puri and Bundi after pressing it.  Have
n't met him for a long time.
Brother, your father is no more.
Hey son, I have come.
Hey Aunt, hello.  Hey come on aunty, sit down.
Come come come quickly.  Aunt, sit down.  Come, come, give me the bag
, give me the bag.
And wait for now.
Sit, sit.   The
climax is yet to come.
Aunty, drink white tea.
[laughter]
Look, son, Mother's Day is coming.
Yes, Aunt
and Papa's Father's Day comes.
Yes aunty.
And see son, your Valentine's Day also
comes.   Yes, no, Aunty.
But see son, no day of our aunts
comes.
Hey aunt, who said your day doesn't come?
Your day is coming.
Which one, son?
Nag Panchami is the day of the serpent.
This guy has started talking too much.  He is
asking more questions.  One day she will have to
show her snake form.  He will have to bite.
[laughter]
Is there a stove?  Yes,
then bake the roti, you
fool,
how did you bake the roti, I do
n't want to take the cylinder, I will get angry
papa, look this man has again chewed my dupatta,
every day someone or the other spoils some clothes,
oh will you put a cage for these humans or
not, I am fed up,
just keep watching, today he will not escape,
oh this man turned out to be very clever, he lost the
bread without getting caught,
why is 15th August celebrated?
Gandhiji gave birth to Modiji.
[laughter]
Attention travelers.  There is a gate on the right.   The
train is two hours late from its scheduled time.   Will
take it down from top.  Your mouth and ears will
be torn apart.  Without a ticket, they will chase you and beat you on the platform.
Oh my god.   I have
applied redness on my lips.  Your sister-in-law is also with me.  Don't
push.  The entire car is empty.   Well, I had
left this much behind.   She
will arrive two-three minutes late.  TT will come to check the ticket.
23 12 train will arrive at platform number one.
Injustice was done.   Will
take it down from top.  The evil eye will be removed from you.   If you move it
here and there, she will beat you like a roller.
Our mom and dad knew it.
So sir, I am making a map of your house.
Yes.
As there will be entry at the entrance, I am
providing a latrine here.  [laughter]
I'm from the latrine, the kidnapped latrine?  If
your guests come from outside, they will freshen up here only.
Yes, that is probably right.
A room next door.
Ok.  And here I am giving you a
toilet.
So you will have a kitchen here.
Yes.
And there will be a small toilet inside the kitchen.
Build a house and make a toilet.
Like the hall.  TV is also installed.
Some lakhs gap long number short number.  So
where is the
lighting, I
saw it like this, so sir, your
map is completely ready,
your signature is required for the agreement, if you do
n't give your signature, I like it very much, I
eat and drink alone, cancel it, oh ignorant
illiterate,
okay, but I put my thumb impression
[laughs]
brother, should I give my earnings to my wife or not, should I not give it,
brother, because in the old times,
elders used to say that if you
give your earnings to your wife, there will be prosperity in the house.  And if you give your
earnings to your wife in today's times,
parcels will come to your house.  Sometimes
from Flipkart, sometimes from Zomato, sometimes from Meesho.  [laughter]
When did our country become independent?
Who knows sir, we were not there.  Had gone to her parents' house.
Okay Babu, why do we hoist the flag
?   To
eat laddus.
Okay Babu, do you recognize him?  What were these?
Bald.
Gave them freedom.  [laughter]
And wait a minute.  The climax is yet to come.
[laughs]
Oh dear,
how much is it? It's
₹10.
How much is it costing you?   It is
costing me ₹8.
Then why are you selling it for Rs 10?
[nasal sound]
Hey, I will earn ₹2.
So God has given us hands and legs to earn money.
Work, work hard.  Why are you being dishonest about
₹2?
I have opened this shop to earn money and
what else am I doing?
Yes, yes, this is some work, it is
not completely dishonest for ₹2.
Hey [laughter] brother, what are you looking for?  Get me married.
Why should I get you married?
Then why are you asking what do you want?
Hey brother, I am asking you
what do you want from the shop?  [laughs]
So brother, give me one chip but without any dishonesty for
₹8.
Oh brother, no chips for ₹8.  It is worth ₹10.  If you want to take it,
take it, otherwise go away from here.  Don't eat my brain.   Okay, I am
not bothering you.  Give me the chips.  I will
eat chips.
But
I strongly hate those who love dishonestly for ₹1.
Why?  What happened sister?  Is it some
old thing?
Hey sister, will your hair be cut now?
Yes, they will be cut.  Sit now for 15-20 minutes.   I
will sit, sister, but I will get bored.   Can
I play your sound?
Yes, yes, this is definitely something worth asking.
And wait for now.  The climax is yet to come, I have no
doubt [Music]
Hey, what song did you play? Play a song from our times. The
wife should match the vibe. Hey friend,
sister, you should have told me earlier. I would have played a good song. Here,
listen to this after
cutting the hair
[Laughter]
Brother,
tell me, do you like the boy?
Look, whatever I say, I will say it openly that I do
n't like the boy at all.
How can you not like this?  And whoever comes, goes away after
consuming drugs.  At least you
like it.
Hey, if you don't like it then it's not there.
But why not?  Firstly, it looks
black.  He is thin from above.
How will our girl adjust?
And wait for now.  The climax is yet to come.   I was
insulted.
Wait, be patient.
Wait, we will give the dowry instead.
[Music] If you do
n't like it [laughter] then you don't like it
[laughter]
brother, you can hit me more, hit me more, brother, you are a
lion, a lioness,
you are a Hijra, a Hijri, a
Hijra,
what are you thinking, [ __ ], it's not right for you to say it, just
say it [laughter]
friend Fatima, my voice is not good, you can play it,
wait, I am putting it on speaker,
and wait, the climax is still left, and
you are saying this
[laughter] what is this
brother,
welcome to the program to attract money.  The very first step is to
light a candle.
Good.
Remember to light the candle with a matchstick.
But if you have lit it with a lighter then
you cannot extinguish it.
[laughter] Don't relight a candle that's been extinguished.
This will have the opposite effect.
If you have lit the candle and then extinguished it again,
it will have an even worse effect.
[laughter]
Take another chance.  Light the candle again.
Remember to light the candle with a lighter this time.
[laughter]
Don't blow out the candle and then light it again with a lighter,
or you'll become even poorer.
If you have blown out the candle again this time, then it
proves
that you are not worthy of becoming rich.
Hey, if you want to do something big in life, then
listen to your heart and your mind, kick away those
people who give you advice.  I felt a
strong shock.   Getting
ready like a groom.  Where are you planning to go
?  He will eat food first and then go somewhere.
Listen sister, will you go like a storm or will you
come like a hurricane?
Good.
Coming in 5 minutes now.  We will eat food later.   He
says it will take 5 minutes and then takes 5 hours.  Wait, let me
tell dad now.   If
we say 5 minutes, we come back in 5 minutes.
Like you, I don't spend 10 hours speaking for 10 minutes.
[screaming]
How is it going to take 10 hours anyway?  There should
also be a 10-hour face.
We are boys, we don't take leave without any reason.
And how will it take 10 hours?   I do
n't put putty on my face like you.
First of all, it's called a makeup kit, not a putty.
You will always remain an idiot.
My body scent is more expensive than your makeup kit.
And I have seen my face.
Asian paint for walls is better than you.
Listen, listen, write down what I am saying
quickly.  Wait a minute.  Yes, just a minute.
Yes yes, speak, speak, speak.
Nine what?  Are there eight
?  What are you saying?   Wait a minute.
Four
patience.
Five what?
Okay,
three to
hi?
Hi.
Okay to 7 to thank you, thank you.   Wait a minute.
Thank you so much.  The climax is yet to come.   What are you saying, what are
we
saying, nine or five?  four
[laughs] five what good
three to five good to
thank you thank you.
[laughter] Can
you even pluck the moon and stars for me
?
Hey, I don't know what all I might break for you.
Hey brother,
your husband is so romantic.
And wait for now.  The climax is yet to come.
If you love me, then
bring me the moon and stars tonight.   I will not
wait till night for you.  I
can still bring the moon and stars.
How is it?
Why did you break me?
You are my silver.  [laughs]
So guys, let
me know in the comments which part of this you enjoyed the most.
And yes, don't forget to like Guy's video
and subscribe to Guy's channel.  Hey, please
comment,
you guys please comment,
I work so hard for you.  Do you
even know what time it is now?  It's so late at night
I'm shooting for you guys so
I can upload the video.  Please comment,
friend.  Like it, comment on it and
a hype option will appear on the side.  Click on that too
and if you haven't subscribed then it's a
must.  Don't
forget to subscribe.  Friends, let's meet
in the next video.  Till then,
bye-bye.